UTU Additional Records 6023
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UTU Additional Records
1921-1948
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Transportation Union (UTU)
6023
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5767529
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 10, 2016
EAD encoding:
Elizabeth Parker, April 29, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3012: Alice Cook Papers /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4040: George H. Hildebrand Papers /4055: James O. Morris Office Files /4064: Kurt Hanslowe Papers /4073: James O. Morris Office Files /4139: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4148: George W. Brooks Additional Papers /4164: Harrison M. Trice Additional Papers /4212: Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence 5007: U.S. Emergency Board No. 175 Transcripts and Exhibits 5027: U.S. Emergency Board No. 178 Transcripts 5034: Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034 MB: Switchmen's Union of North America Memorabilia 5034 P: Switchmen's Union of North America Photographs 5084: Switchmen's Union of North America Additional Records 5139: UTU Records 5139 AV: UTU Audio-Visual Material 5139 MB: UTU Memorabilia 5139 P: UTU Photographs 5141: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5141 G: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Graphics 5141 MB: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Memorabilia 5141 P: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Photographs 5148: Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen Records 5148 MB: Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen Memorabilia 5148 P: Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen Photographs 5164: UTU Canada Records 5173: John Collins Collection of Railway Labor Records 5183: Edward Heisler Collection of Southern Pacific Railroad Operating Crafts Union Organizing Documents 5189: Labor Song Books 5194: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Files 5196: UTU Ladies' Auxiliary Iowa Joint Board Minutes 5197: Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Miscellany 5197 MB: Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Memorabilia 5203: Grace McDonald Papers 5203: Grace McDonald Papers
Transport workers -- Labor unions; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Sources; United Transportation Union
5767529
- Presentation Made by the American Federation of Labor Before the United States Railroad Labor Board, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Part One. Chicago, Illinois. Bound.
- Presentation Made by the American Federation of Labor Before the United States Railroad Labor Board, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Part Two, Volume One. Chicago, Illinois. Bound.
- Presentation Made by the American Federation of Labor Before the United States Railroad Labor Board, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Part Two, Volume Two. Chicago, Illinois. Bound.
- The Problem of Piece Work (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Chicago, Illinois. No date. Bound.
- Argument and Brief Submitted on Behalf of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  May 1920. Bound.
- Statements Made by the Association of Railway Executives Conference Committee of Managers Before the United States Railroad Labor Board, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  May 17-June 4, 1920. Bound.
- Statements Made by the Association of Railway Executives Conference Committee of Managers before the United States Railroad Labor Board, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Volume Two. Chicago, Illinois. Bound. January 10-18, 1921
- Statements Made by the Association of Railway Executives Conference Committee of Managers before the United States Railroad Labor Board, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Volume Three. Chicago, Illinois. Bound. January 31-February 2, 1921.
- Statements Made by the Association of Railway Executives Conference Committee of Managers before the United States Railroad Labor Board, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Volume Four. Chicago, Illinois. Bound. February 2-3, 1921.
- Statements Made by the Association of Railway Executives Conference Committee of Managers before the United States Railroad Labor Board, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Volume Five. Chicago, Illinois. Bound. February 7-8, 1921.
- Tabulation Showing Number of Carriers Agreeing or Disagreeing to 42 of the Major Rules Contained in the National Agreement Covering Maintenance of Way Employees and Shop Laborers, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  November 26, 1921. Bound.
- Minutes of Meetings between the Special Conference Committee of the Railways and the Switchmen's Union of North America, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  June 12, 1917. Bound.
- Nickel Rate Road: The New York, Chicago, and Saint Louis Railroad Company - First, Second, and Third Series of Mechanical Questions for Examination of Locomotive Firemen (Box 1, Folder 13)
  No Date. Bound.
- Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board: Saint Louis-San Francisco Railway, et al. versus Various Classes of Employees (Docket 353), 1921 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Chicago, Illinois. Bound. Thursday, April 28, 1921.
- Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board: Saint Louis-San Francisco Railway, et al. versus Various Classes of Employees (Docket 353), 1921 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Bound. Chicago, Illinois. May 2, 1921.
- Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board: Saint Louis-San Francisco Railway, et al. versus Various Classes of Employees (Docket 353), 1921 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Bound. Chicago, Illinois. May 4, 1921.
- Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board: Saint Louis-San Francisco Railway, et al. versus Various Classes of Employees (Docket 353), 1921 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Bound. Chicago, Illinois. May 5, 1921.
- Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board: Saint Louis-San Francisco Railway, et al. versus Various Classes of Employees (Docket 353), 1921 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Bound. Chicago, Illinois. May 6, 1921.
- Proceedings of the United States Railroad Labor Board: Saint Louis-San Francisco Railway, et al. versus Various Classes of Employees (Docket 353), 1921 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Bound. Chicago, Illinois. May 7, 1921.
- Report to the President by the Emergency Board: To Investigate Unadjusted Disputes Concerning Rates of Pay and Working Rules, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  January 27, 1948. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Volume One. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Volume Two. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Volume Three. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Volume Four. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Volume Five. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Volume Six. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Volume Seven. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Volume Eight. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Volume Nine. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Volume Ten. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Volume Eleven. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Volume Twelve. Bound.
- Transcripts of Proceedings of the Emergency Board - To Investigate and Report on Certain Differences between Certain Western Railroads and the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Volume Thirteen. Bound.